声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon sealovemoon憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
他能活下来吗?
Do you think he's gonna live?
你认识他?
Do you know him?
他坐在我旁边
He was sitting next to me.
你以为他们会来吗
You'd think they would have come by now.
-谁?  -谁都行
-Who?  -Anyone.
这和跳棋一样吗?
What is it, like checkers?
不太一样  它比跳棋好玩
Not really. It's a better game than checkers.
两个人游戏  分两边
Two players, two sides.
一方白子  一方黑子
One is light, one is dark.
Walt...
你想知道个秘密吗?
Do you want to know a secret?
不要相信她
Don't trust her.
她是个危险人物
She's dangerous.
不要动
Try not to move, man.
我要找到她
I have to find her.
我要把她带回来
I have to bring her back.
好吧  你继续说吧
Yeah, you keep saying that.
每次我问你把谁带回来时
And every time I ask you who you have to bring back,
你都会昏过去
you pass out on me again.
因为你在发高烧
Since your fever's running pretty high,
所以我猜你跟本不知道你在说谁
I'm guessing you have no idea who the hell you're talking about.
我的手铐
My cuffs.
My handcuffs.
我的手铐在哪?
Where are my cuffs?
什么?
What?
我的外衣兜
My jacket pocket.
-我不...  -我的外衣兜
-I don't...-My jacket pocket.
好吧
Okay.
危险
Dangerous.
她是危险人物
She's dangerous.
天开始黑了
It's getting dark.
那就加快脚步
Then pick up the pace.
-乡巴佬  -你敢再大点声?
-Hick.  -A little louder?
我们应该在这露营
We should make camp.
-什么  在这?  -是的  在这
-What, here?  -Yes, here.
我不会停下来的  你们在这好好的野餐一顿吧
I'm not stopping. Y'all have a nice cookout.
很好  在夜里穿过丛林
Excellent. Walk through the jungle in the dark.
怕树会吃了我们吗?
Ooh, afraid the trees are gonna get us?
不会  但摧毁树的东西会吃了你
No. What is knocking down the trees will get you.
好啊  你这么担心我
Well, you're so worried about me,
为什么不把弹夹给我?
how about you give me the clip back?
把枪收起来  Sawyer
Put your gun back in your pants, Sawyer.
Sayids是对的  如果继续走你也回不到沙滩的
Sayid's right. You keep walking, you're not gonna make it to the beach.
为什么
Yeah, why's that?
相信我
Trust me.
这是澳大利亚
This is Australia.
这是我们
This is us.
不错的棍子
Nice stick.
两天前  我们从悉尼起飞
Two da ago, we take off from Sydney.
我们沿着所有飞往洛杉矶的
We fly along the same northeast route
商务客机的东北航线飞行
every commercial airliner bound for los angeles does.
那个驾驶员  他说他和地面失去了联系  对吧?
Now, the pilot, he said he lost communication with the ground, correct?
是的  有6个小时
Yeah, six hours in.
他就调头驶向斐济了
He turned around and headed for Fiji.
就是说我们改变了航线
So he changed course.
遗憾的是  没人知道我们改变了航线
Regrettably, no one knew he changed course.
然后遇到了气流
The turbulence hit.
下面的事我们都知道了
We know the rest.
那个飞行员说我们离航线有一千多英里远
The pilot said we were over 1,000 miles off course.
没错  但他们会找到我们的
Yeah, but they'll find us.
他们的卫星可以清楚的拍到你的车牌号码
They have satellites in space that can take pictures of your license plate.
如果我们都带着车牌就行
If only we were all wearing license plates.
你可是个悲观主义者
Well, aren't you the pessimist.
基本的摄影技巧...对准然后再拍
Basic photography...point and shoot.
卫星是可以拍照  但它们要知道拍哪
Satellites can shoot,but they must be told where to point.
妈的
Bollocks.
戏做的不错  很好看
Okay, really enjoyed the puppet show. Fantastic.
我们被困在了一个无人知晓的地方
So we're stuck in the middle of damn nowhere.
我们谈谈别的怎么样?
How about we talk about that other thing?
无线电接收器收到的信号
You know, the transmission Abdul picked up on his little radio.
那法国婊子说"他们都死了"
The French chick that said "they're all dead."
信号已经发射了... 多长时间  Kate?
The transmission's been on a loop for...how long was it, freckles?
-16年  -没错
-16 years.  -Right.
我们谈谈这个吧
Let's talk about that.
我们回去要把这些告诉大家
Well, we have to tell the others when we get back.
-告诉他们什么?  -我们所听到的
-Tell them what exactly?  -What we heard.
你听到什么了?  我可不是个愚蠢的翻译
You didn't hear anything. I'm not a stupid translator.
谁也不可以告诉大家任何事
No one's going to tell them anything.
散播我们所听到的
To relay what we heard
却又没有完全理解的东西  会造成大家的恐慌
without fully understanding it will cause a panic.
如果我们告诉他们我们知道的
If we tell them what we know,
我们就会带走他们的希望
we take away their hope.
失掉希望是件很可怕的事情
And hope is a very dangerous thing to lose.
所以我们要说谎
So we lie.
-是恐龙吗?  -不是恐龙
-Was it a dinosaur?  -It wasn't a dinosaur.
你说你没看见它?
You said you didn't see it.
没有
I didn't.
那你怎么知道它不是恐龙?
So how do you know it wasn't a dinosaur?
因为恐龙已经灭绝了
Because dinosaurs are extinct.
他怎么样了?
So what's his story?
他看起来像是...
He looks kind of...
快死了
dying.
-他不会死的  -伤口已经化脓了
-He's not gonna die.  -He's yellow, man.
他的伤口是感染了  但抗生素会解决的
His wound is infected, but the antibiotics will fight it off.
如果它们解决不了呢?
hat if they don't?
那他的身体就停止工作了
Then his body will shut down
一件一件的停止
one piece at a time.
他的腹部开始僵化  然后...
His abdomen goes rigid, then...
看起来他很疼
He looks like he's in pain.
这是什么?
What's this?
老兄?
Dude?
你认为她做了什么?
What do you think she did?
这不关我的事
It's none of my business.
-她看起来像中坚分子  -Hurley
-She looks pretty hardcore.  -Hurley.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我在站岗
I'm standing guard.
你听到他们是怎么说的吗?
You heard what they said's out there.
你从没拿过枪的  他是反对枪的
You've never even held a gun. He doesn't believe in guns.
-他去游行过  -我没游行过
-He goes on marches.  -I don't go on marches.
是的  把它给Al-jazeera  他会保护我们的
Yeah, give it to Al-jazeera. He'll protect us.
Al-jazeera是一种网络
Al-jazeera's a network.
-让我来保管  -我们应该给她
-I'll keep the damn gun.  -We should give it to her.
是的
Yeah.
枪应该由Kate保管
Kate should hold the gun.
我同意
Fine with me.
好啊?
Well?
-早安  -早安
-Good morning.  -Morning.
你睡在了我的羊圏里
You're sleeping in my sheep pen.
对不起
Sorry.
你怎么来这的?
How'd you get here?
-走来的  -你走来的?
-I walked.  -You walked?
-是的  -从哪?
-Yeah.  -From where?
-小镇  -离这最近的小镇也有15公里
-Town.  -Nearest town's 15 kilometers.
也许正因如此我才这么累吧
Maybe that's why I'm so exhausted.
你叫什么?
What's your name?
Annie
你饿吗  Annie?
You hungry, Annie?
想告诉我你为什么侵入我的地方吗?
So, you want to tell me why you're trespassing on my property?
我钱用光了
I ran out of money.
你是美国人?
You're an American?
加拿大人
Canadian.
我大学毕业后  想出去见见世界
I graduated from college and figured I'd see the world.
澳大利亚是我最想去的  所以我就登上了去墨尔本的飞机
Australia was top of my list,so I hopped a flight to Melbourne,
但我这里没有一个熟人
but I don't know anybody here,
所以我就到处走了走
so I just figured I'd walk for a while,you know?
墨尔本离这有几百公里
Melbourne's a hundred kilometers from here.
我喜欢走路
I like walking.
然后你就走到了我的农场?
And you just happened to wander onto my farm?
我也喜欢农场
I like farms, too.
你知道怎样料理农场吗?
Do you know how to work one?
知道
Yeah.
我妻子8个月前的礼拜三去世了
My wife died eight months ago wednesday.
她为我留下了太多的家务和债务
She left me with too many chores and a hell of a mortgage.
你能帮我处理前者吗?
If you help me with the first one,
我会为你提供住处并付你合理的薪水的
I'll give you a fair wage and a place to stay.
成交
Deal.
我是个左撇子
I'm a lefty.
老兄! 老兄!
Dude ! Dude !
他们回来了
They're back.
正如你们所知道的
As you and the others know,
我们爬上了山,以便帮助救援队找到我们
we hiked up the mountain in an attempt to help the rescue team locate us.
无线电接收器没有收到信号
The transceiver failed to pick up a signal.
我们无法发射求救信号
We weren't able to send out a call for help.
但我们不能放弃
But we're not giving up.
如果我们收集一下电子设备
If we gather electronic equipment
比如手机  笔记本电脑...
your cell phones, laptops...
我可以使信号增强  然后再次尝试
I can boost the signal and we can try again.
但这可能需要一些时间  所以从现在开始
But that may take some time, so for now,
我们要合理分配剩下的食物
we should begin rationing our remaining food.
如果下雨了  我们要撘帆布来收集雨水
If it rains, we should set up tarps to collect water.
我要你们分成3组
I need to organize three separate groups.
每个组都要有个领队
Each group should have a leader.
一组负责找水  由我来负责
One group for water. I'll organize that.
谁来组织收集电子设备?
Who's going to organize electronics?
你...配给食物?
You...rationing food?
好吧
Okay.
我需要第三组来搭设他们的...
And I will need a third group to concern themselves with the construction of...
我  嗯... 我有事要告诉你
I, um... I need to tell you something.
好的
Okay. Sure.
我们不能发射信号是因为
We couldn't send out a signal because
被另外一个信号阻挡了
there was another signal blocking it.
另一个信号...
The other signal...
我们听到了
we heard it.
是一个法国女子的求救信号
It was a distress call from a French woman.
她说其他人都死了
She said that the others were dead.
有东西把他们都杀了
That something had killed them all.
她在岛上独自一人
She was alone on the island.
信号已经发射了16年  Jack
It's been playing for 16 years, Jack.
我需要告诉你
I wanted to tell you.
没别的了?
Anything else?
他怎么样了?
How is he?
那个身中弹片的人
The man with the shrapnel in his side.
形势很严峻
He's touch and go.
他醒了吗?
Did he wake up?
没有  只是在手术时醒了几秒
Nah, just for a few seconds during the surgery.
他说什么了吗?
He say anything?
没
No.
她说什么了?
So what'd she say?
什么都没说
She didn't say anything.
你告诉她你知道了吗
But you told her you knew.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
你知道她的那张疑犯照片
Well, you kinda know she's in that mug shot.
还有那副手铐
And that we found those handcuffs.
那人不停的念叨"她是危险人物"
And that guy keeps mumbling "she's dangerous,she's dangerous" over and over.
这不关我的事  和我无关
It's not my business. Not my problem.
没错  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
等Johnny Fever好了  让他去处理吧
We'll let Johnny Fever take care of her when he gets better.
如果我们找不到更强的抗生素 他不会好起来的
He's not getting better if we don't get some stronger antibiotics.
-我从行李里找到的那个  -那是治耳朵感染和脚气的
-That stuff I got from the luggage... -It's for ear infections and foot fungus.
我都找遍了
I went through everything, man.
上面的机厢里会不会有?
What about that luggage in the overhead compartments?
-那在飞机里面  -怎么了?
-That's inside the plane.  -Yeah?
但尸体也在里面  他们都...
But the bodies are in there,and they're all...
交给我吧,你去照看一下...
Look, I'll handle it.Why don't you keep an eye on...
好  我很愿意  这就去
Great. Yeah, I'd love to. On it.
你在这做什么?
What are you doing in here?
找东西  和你一样
Trick-or-treatin', same as you.
你这是掠夺
You're looting.
随你怎么说
Ahh! You say potato.
你包里是什么?
What's in the bag?
烟  酒  还有几本"花花公子"
Booze, smokes, a couple "playboys."
-你的呢?  -药
-What's in yours?  -Medicine.
我们正好互补  是吧?
Well, just about sums it up, don't it?
你在家也这么做吗?
You do this back home, too?
偷死人的东西?
Steal from the dead?
老兄  醒醒吧  感受一下这里充斥的谎言
Brother, you got to wake up and smell the gull crap here.
救援队不会来的
Rescue ain't coming.
你是在浪费时间
You're just wasting your time,
试着去救一个我上次见到时
trying to save a guy who,last time I checked,
有一个像我头一样大的铁片插在肚子上的人
had a piece of metal the size of my head sticking out of his bread basket.
我来问问你
Let me ask you something.
你要用多少那样的药片才能救活他?
How many of those pills are you going to use to fix him up?
-需要多少就用多少  -是吗?
-As many as it takes.  -Yeah?
你有多少?
How many you got?
你要看看这的情况  医生
You're just not looking at the big picture, doc.
你还活在文明社会
You're still back in civilization.
-是吗?  那你在哪?  -我?
-Yeah? And where are you?  -Me?
我在野生社会
I'm in the wild.
我来吧
I got it.
让我来
谢谢
Thanks.
我来  我来  好的
I got it. I got it. Yeah.
我们要看到光明的一面
Well, look on the bright side.
要是别人遇到这事  状况未必比我们好
Whoever's this was is probably better off than we are.
我来
I got it.
我想我找到你的包了
真的吗?
让我看看
这不是我的
那么我继续找找
你看看你自己
你的衣服 你现在很脏
马上去洗一洗
Sun
我爱你
-孩子怎么样?  -应该没事
-How's the baby?  -It's okay, I think.
很好
Good.
那  你的...
So, your,
你丈夫不在飞机上?
your husband, was he on the flight?
不  我没结婚呢
no, I'm not married.
我知道  我很前卫
I know. How modern of me.
需要男人做什么  对吧?
Well, who needs men, right?
一点用都没有
Bloody useless.
你们爬到山顶上  却一无所获?
So, you guys hiked all the way up on that mountain for nothing, huh?
抱歉
Sorry.
我要去弄些水
I was gonna get some more water.
我们还不认识  我是Kate
We haven't met. I'm Kate.
-你好  Kate  -你好
-Hi, Kate.  -Hi.
Hurley
我在找Jack  以为他会在这
I was just looking for Jack,and I thought he might be in there.
是的...不
Yeah...no.
他去找药去了
He went to go get some medicine.
-哪  机身里?  -什么?
-Where, in the fuselage?-What?
是的  在
Yeah. Yeah, in the,
我要弄水去了
You know, I got to go get that water.
如果你把钱存起来
The bank would have given you a heck of a toaster
银行会奖你一个烤面包机的
if you'd kept that in a savings account.
我要烤面包机做什么?
What do I need a toaster for?
你把工资藏到罐头瓶里去了  Annie
You're hiding your wages in a tin can, Annie.
我是说  我可以替你保管的
I mean, I would have held onto it for you.
我知道怎样安全
I got trust issues.
你不想和我道别吗?
Weren't you gonna say goodbye?
我给你留了张条
I wrote you a note.
你来这已经有三个月了  Annie
You've been here for almost three months, Annie,
每次我问你关于你的事,
and every time I ask you about yourself,
你总是那种眼神
you get that look in your eye.
对  就是这种
Yeah, that one.
所以我就不再问了
So I mind my own business.
我想可能你一时糊涂做了什么坏事
I figured maybe you got off on the wrong side of a bad relationship.
也许你逃了出来
Maybe you ran.
我知道你总有一天会走的
I always knew you'd leave here someday.
可我不希望是在半夜
I guess I hoped it wouldn't be in the middle of the night.
-很抱歉  -是的
-I'm sorry.  -Yeah.
我也是
So am I.
Annie  你为什么不再多呆一晚呢?
Annie, why don't you just stay one more night, eh?
明天一早我会送你去火车站的
I'll drive you to the train station first thing in the morning.
我保证
I promise.
好
Good.
我知道的
I get it, you know.
每人都应得一个崭新的开始
Everyone deserves a fresh start.
放开她,妈的!
Let her go, damn it!
呼吸!  快!
Breathe! Come on!
快  快
Come on, come on.
看着我!  看...
Look at me! Look...
你做什么了?
What did you do?
我只是看看他...
I was just checking to see if he was...
他就扑向我
He jumped on me.
他...没事吧?
Is he... okay?
他对这些抗生素都没反应
He's not responding to any antibiotics,
他内部在流血  他烧到40度了
he's bleeding internally,his fever's pushing 104,
他腹部僵化了
and his abdomen's rigid.
他需要水
He needs water.
你要怎么处置?
So what are you going to do about it?
-处置什么?  -处置他
-About what?  -About him.
我告诉过你  他需要水
I told you, he needs water.
他会很痛苦吗?
Will he suffer?
会很快吗?
Will it be quick?
不  不会很快
No, it won't be quick.
两天  三天  也许四天
Two, three, maybe four days.
他会感觉到吗?
And he'll feel it?
是的  他会的
Yeah, he'll feel it.
你不能让他脱离痛苦吗?
Can't you put him out of his misery?
我看过你的疑犯照片了  Kate
I saw your mug shot, Kate.
我不是杀人犯
I am not a murder.
你在加拿大听Patsy Cline的歌吗?
Don't listen to Patsy Cline in Canada?
哪里的人都听Patsy Cline的歌
They listen to Patsy Cline everywhere.
你饿吗?
You hungry?
-我会在火车上吃的  -你确定?
-I'll eat on the train.  -You sure?
前面有个地方卖汉堡
A little place up here makes a mean burger.
-你在看什么  Ray?  -什么?
-What are you looking for, Ray?  -What?
我没有  只是...
I'm not. Just...
你知道多久了?
How long have you known?
没几天
Couple of days.
我在邮局看到了你的照片
I saw your picture in the post office.
我想他们可能知道你在澳大利亚
I guess they knew you were down under.
为什么?
Why?
奖金有$23,000
The reward's $23,000.
当我见到你的时候告诉过你  我欠了好多的债务
I told you when I met you. I got a hell of a mortgage.
如果这会让你感觉好点的话
If it makes you feel any better,
这是个很艰难的决定  Annie
it was a hard decision, Annie.
我不叫Annie
My name's not Annie.
那个和你在一起的人是谁?
who's that guy you were hanging out with?
那个秃顶的
You know, the bald guy.
-Locke先生?  -Locke先生
-Oh, mr. Locke?  -Mr. Locke.
-Locke先生有孩子吗?  -他没说
-Mr. Locke got any kids?  -He didn't say.
-那他说什么了?  -我不知道
-Yeah, what did he say?  -I don't know.
什么叫你不知道?  他说什么了?
What do you mean, you don't know? What did he say?
-一些秘密  -他告诉你不要告诉我?
-Some of it's secret.  -He tell you not to tell me?
-没有  -那是什么秘密?
-No.  -Then what's the secret?
Locke先生说这里发生了奇迹
Mr. Locke said a miracle happened here.
没错  在我们每人身上都发生了奇迹  Walt
Yeah, well, a miracle happened to all of us, Walt.
我们是飞机坠毁的幸存者
We survived the plane crash.
我不想让你再和他在一起了
Look, I don't want you hanging around him anymore.
为什么?  我们是朋友
Why not? He's my friend.
我也是你的朋友
Hey, I'm your friend, too.
如果你是我朋友  你就去找Vincent了
If you're my friend, you'd find Vincent.
Walt...
我没有放弃寻找你的狗
Look, I haven't given up on your dog.
我会尽一切努力去找它的
I'm gonna do everything I can to find him.
-不  你不会  -不  Walt  我会的
-No, you won't.-Yeah, Walt, I will.
你不关心Vincent
You don't care about Vincent.
雨一停我就去找你的狗
I'm gonna get your dog back as soon as it stops raining.
好吧  听我说  我会把你的狗找回来的
Okay, listen to me.I'm gonna get your dog back.
"雨一停就去"
"As soon as it stops raining."
好  真好
Good. Nice.
我要找到你的狗
I'm gonna find your dog.
我正在穿过这该死的恐怖的丛林
Yeah, I'm just gonna go walking through the haunted damn jungle
为你找...
looking for your...
Vincent?
Vincent?  是你吗?
Vincent? That you, buddy?
有东西在  追我  所以...
Something was,  chasing me, so,
我现在听不见它了
Yeah, I don't hear it now.
但你应该
but you should probably
回...去
head... back.
我什么都没看见
I didn't see anything.
如果你担心的话
You know, if you're worried about it,
我  我什么都没看见
I...I didn't see anything.
-你在做什么?  -口哨
-What are you making?  -A whistle.
我在录音的时候用过一次部落的长笛
I used some tribal flutes once in a recording session.
我是搞乐队的
I'm in a band.
我真希望他已经死了
I wish he would just die already.
人道一点  Shannon
Real humane, Shannon.
我能帮忙吗?
Anything I can do to help?
不  我很好  谢谢
No, I'm good. Thanks.
其他人开始烦躁了
The others are getting upset.
他们想知道帐篷发生什么事了
They want to know what's going on inside the tent.
我在救他的命
I'm trying to save his life.
谣言说你办不到
Rumor has it you can't.
需要火吗?
You need a light?
我是来谢你的
Came by to thank you.
-你要问为什么吗?  -为什么?
-You gonna ask what for?  -What for?
因为你把那枪从我这拿走了
For taking that gun away from me.
-我没从你那拿走  -它不是在你腰上别的吗?
-I didn't take it away from you.  -Stickin' out of your denims, ain't it?
我现在真的不想拿那把枪了
Sure wouldn't want to be the one with that gun right now.
因为整晚大家都听到那人的呻吟
'Cause everyone sitting out there listening that poor boy scream all night
都知道应该做什么
knows what's got to be done.
可只有一个人能办到  就是拿枪的人
Only one that can do it is the one with that gun.
不要表现得这么惊奇
Don't act so surprised.
我听到你跟那英雄说了同样的话
I heard you tell hero the same thing.
里面只剩一颗子弹了
Hell, there's only one bullet left.
为大家做点好事吧
Be damn near poetic.
-听我说...  -不  你不要讲话
-Listen to me...  -No, you need to keep quiet.
听我说
Listen to me.
不管她做什么  不管她让你怎么感觉
No matter what she does,no matter how she makes you feel,
就是...
just don't...
不要相信她的话
trust a word that she says.
她会用任何办法逃走
She will do anything to get away.
她做了什么?
What did she do?
-我要和她谈谈  -告诉我她做了什么
-I want to talk to her.  -Tell me what she did.
我要单独和她谈谈
I want to talk to her alone.
她也把你骗了,啊?
She got to you, too, huh?
Kate
什么事?
What was it?
-什么?  -你的忙
-What?  -The favor.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
飞机坠毁前我听到的最后一句话  你让我帮你个忙
Last thing I heard before the crash,you wanted a favor.
女士们  先生们  驾驶员刚开启了 "请扣好安全带"指示灯
Ladies and gentlemen, the captain has switched on the "fasten seatbelts" sign.
请回到你的座位  并扣好安全带
Please return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
-我想要你帮个忙  -真的?
-I have one favor to ask.  -Really?
这很好
This ought to be good.
什么?
Well?
我想让你保证Ray Mullen能拿到他的两万三千元奖金
I wanted you to make sure that Ray Mullen got his 23 grand.
什么  那个供出你的人?
What, the guy who ratted you out?
他欠了好多的债务
He had a hell of a mortgage.
你还是那样
You really are one of a kind.
如果你不救他  你可以跑掉的
You know, you would have got away if hadn't saved him.
也许你没察觉到  我已经跑掉了
In case you hadn't noticed, I did get away.
在我看来你还没有
You don't look free to me.
Kate  我就要死了  对吗?
Kate, I'm gonna die, right?
是的
Yeah.
那么...你会做吗?
So...are you gonna do it,
还是不会?
or what?
逃犯在哪呢?
So, where's the fugitive?
帐篷里
In the tent.
你让她自己去那里?
You let her in there alone?
她能做什么?
What's she gonna do?
-一个120磅的女人  -是的  但她有枪
-She's 120 pounds soaking wet.  -Yeah, but she's got that gun.
-什么?  -她带着的
-What?  -She's strapped, man.
我看见了  在她的...她的...
I saw it in her...in her...in her
-你做了什么?  -有什么不能做的
-What did you do?  -What you couldn't.
作为一名医生  我知道你应该做什么
Look, I get where you're coming from,being a doctor and all.
但是他想这样的  是他要我做的
But he wanted it. Hell, he asked me.
我不比你更喜欢做这个
So I don't like it any more than you do,
但有些事是一定要有人去做的
but something had to be done.
我的天
no way.
伙计们
Guys.
你朝他胸部射的?
You shot him in the chest?
我瞄的是他的心脏
I was aiming for his heart.
你没打中
You missed.
他还在呼吸吗?
Is he still breathing ?
你射穿了他的肺  要用几小时他才会失血而死
You perforated his lung.It'll take hours to bleed out.
可是...只有一颗子弹
There was...only had one bullet.
出去!  出去!
Get out. Get out!
该死!
Damn it!
我找到了你儿子的狗
I found your son's dog.
什么?
What?
Vincent?
我把它绑在那边的树上了
I tethered him to a tree just over there.
我知道Walt失去了他的母亲
I know that Walt lost his mom.
我想应该你把他的狗带给他
I thought that you should be one
多谢
Thanks
我想告诉你我做了什么
I want to tell you what I did.
他为什么要抓我
Why he was after me.
我不想知道
I don't wanna know.
没关系的  Kate
It doesn't matter, Kate,
我们曾经是谁
who we were,
在这之前  在飞机失事之前
what we did before this,
做过什么事
before the crash
都不重要...
it doesn't really...
三天前我们都死了
Three days ago, we all died
我们应该重新再来
We should all be able to start over.
好吧
Okay.
好吗?
Okay?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====